Guide to the Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers WAG.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984., 32447
  - Hughes, Charles, 1982; 32505 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kiefer, Mildred, 1970; 32504 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kramer, Leo, 1982; 32503 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Lindenthal, Nat, 1982; 32502 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Lustig, Richard, 1973; 32501 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Maher, Edward, 1979; 32500 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Perkel, Bertram "Buddy", 1982; 32499 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Reif, Elliot, 1978-1979; 32498 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Roberts, Lillian, Undated; 32497 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Rose, Bert, Undated; 32496 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ross, Phil, Undated; 32495 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Schleicher, Bill, 1981; 32494 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Shalala, Donna, Undated; 32493 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Staff interviews, Undated; 32492 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1982; 32491 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Stephens, Bernie, 1980; 32490 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Topol, Julius, Undated; 32489 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Toto, John and Gary Foster, 1978-1980; 32488 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Varner, Louis, 1982; 32487 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Viani, Alan, 1982; 32486 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Lester, 1982; 32485 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wurf, Jerome "Jerry", 1974-1979; 32484 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Wurf, Jerome "Jerry", 1982; 32483 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Locals: General, 1957-1983; 32482 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General: Leaflets, Newsletters, 1978; 32481 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Maritime Port Council, 1961-1974; 32480 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Membership By Locals, Undated; 32479 (Box 5, Folder 10a)
  - Local 154, NYC Employees, 1957-1965; 32478 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 237, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1966-1968; 32477 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local 237, Teamsters v. Local 1783, Housing Authority, 1957-1964; 32476 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Local 299, Recreational Employees, 1957-1964; 32475 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local 371, Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), 1965; 32474 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1966; 32473 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1967-1972; 32472 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Local 371, SSEU Strike, Undated; 32471 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1961-1965; 32470 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1968-1978; 32469 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1973-1974; 32468 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local 372, School Lunch Aides, 1965; 32467 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Local 374, NY/Brooklyn Botanical Garden, 1957-1973; 32466 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local 376, Parks Department, 1967-1978; 32465 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local 384, CUNY, 1957-1975; 32464 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local 442, Subway Supervisors, 1961-1964; 32463 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local 824, Laborers, 1965; 32462 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local 924-376, Laborers, Undated; 32461 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local 983, Motor Vehicle Operator's Strike, 1956-1967; 32460 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local 1070, Judicial Conference, 1961-1965; 32459 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Local 1087, Bureau of Community Education, Prevailing Rate, 1956-1965; 32458 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Local 1113, Finance Employees, 1958-1966; 32457 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Local 1306, Museum of Natural History, 1956-1974; 32456 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Local 1321-1482, Queensborough Public Library, 1966-1971; 32455 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Local 1320, Public Works, 1957-1963; 32454 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Local 1396, Triborough Bridge and Tunnel, Undated; 32453 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Local 1407, Accountants, 1962-1964; 32452 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Local 1501, New York Zoo, 1956-1961; 32451 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Local 1503, Metropolitan Museum, 1959-1974; 32450 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Local 1549, CWA Raid, 1965-1974; 32449 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Local 1597, Custodial Employees, 1960-1966; 32448 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Series VI: Chapter Drafts., 32427
  - Chapter Headings, Undated; 32446 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Early Years, to 1950, Chapter 1, drafts, Undated; 32445 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - We Have Faith in You, Chapter 2, drafts, Undated; 32444 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Who Built This Union, Robert Moses, Chapter 3, drafts, Undated; 32443 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining, Not Collective Begging, Chapter 4, drafts, Undated; 32442 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Never Again in Awe of Power, Chapter 5, drafts, Undated; 32441 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - You Can Fight City Hall, Chapter 7, drafts, Undated; 32440 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hospital Elections, Chapter 8, drafts, Undated; 32439 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining: Seat of Power, Chapter 9, drafts, Undated; 32438 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gotbaum Takes Command, Chapter 10, drafts, Undated; 32437 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Inside Union Bureaucracy, Chapter 11, draft, Undated; 32436 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Political Machine…Union Made, Chapter 12, drafts, Undated; 32435 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Operation Price Watch, former Chapter 12, draft, Undated; 32434 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Political Participation, Chapter 13, drafts, Undated; 32433 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Learn, Baby Learn…, Chapter 14, drafts, Undated; 32432 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Expanding Union Services, Chapter 15, drafts, Undated; 32431 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - In the Shadow of the Crisis, Chapter 16, drafts, Undated; 32430 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Fiscal Crisis - Threat and Response, Chapter 17, drafts, Undated; 32429 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Contest of Power, Chapter 18, drafts, Undated; 32428 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Series VII: Unprocessed Files, 1940s-2000., 31770
  - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1980s; 32426 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ADA National Board, 1980s; 32425 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ADA Nassau County, Roskoff and Leon Shull Meeting, 1982-1984; 32424 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Grass Roots Insurgency - Wurf v. Zander (1964), 1980s; 32423 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Shier, Carl, 1980s; 32422 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pollard Case, 1991; 32421 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Students, 1979-1984; 32420 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Summer Lease, Kaufman-Morgenstein, 1990-1991; 32419 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Universal Utilities, 1989-1990; 32418 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Warschauer Society: Jack Weinstein, 1991; 32417 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bush Administration: 1 Year Review, 1990; 32416 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1991; 32415 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Credit Charges Summary, 1991; 32414 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Credit Charges (World Pass), 1989; 32413 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dershowitz/American Jewish Congress, 1991; 32412 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IRA (PSC/CUNY and Chemical), 1987-1989; 32411 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IRA Transfer, 1990; 32410 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - ADA New York City, 1982-1984; 32409 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ADA National Board, 1984; 32408 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ADA Nassau County, 1980s; 32407 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ADA State Board, 1979-1982; 32406 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ADA New York, 1981; 32405 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ADA Open Letter: Alan Roskoff, 1981; 32404 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ADA Long Island Executive Committee Meeting, 1985; 32403 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ADA Long Island Membership, 1986-1990; 32402 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ADA long Island Activities, 1988-1990; 32401 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ADA Long Island Bank Balances and Dues, 1988; 32400 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ADA Long Island Activities, 1988; 32399 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ADA: Alan Roskoff, Undated; 32398 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Isaccs, Amy, 1989-1990; 32397 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - ADA Convention: Israeli Resolution, 1990; 32396 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cimitile, Carole, 1989-1990; 32395 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ADA, NYS and Long Island Checking Account, 1980s; 32394 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - ADA; Homeless Housing, Long Island, 1990; 32393 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: ADA, 1992; 32392 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - ADA Long Island, 1989-1990; 32391 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - ADA NYS May Meeting, 1990; 32390 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Mailing Zip Codes, 1984; 32389 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Organizations, 1980s; 32388 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - McTiernan, Jack: Syracuse, 1987-1988; 32387 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Mittermeyer, Paul: Rochester, 1987; 32386 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence: ADA National Office, 1990; 32385 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - ADA NYS, 1990; 32384 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - ADA NYS Billings, 1990; 32383 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - ADA NYS Lobbyist, 1990; 32382 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - ADA NYS Mailings, 1988-1990; 32381 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Sheffer, Ethel, 1990; 32380 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - ADA: Ethel Sheffer Report, 1990; 32379 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - ADA Summer Correspondence, 1990; 32378 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Bowest Corporation (Mortgage), 1991; 32377 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - American Jewish Committee: Task Force on Pluralism, 1988; 32376 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Olicker, Ethel, 1991; 32375 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - ADA National Exec. Committee: Kosovo Resolutions, 1999; 32374 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Liu, Liming (Insurance), 1991; 32373 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Luba, Sy (a/c), Undated; 32372 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - New York Labor History Association (NYLHA), 1998; 32371 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - NYLHA: February 23, 1998; 32370 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - NYLHA: January 13, 1998; 32369 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - NYLHA Minutes and Correspondence, 1997; 32368 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - NYLHA Conference, 1998; 32367 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - ADA: NGO Representative, 1995; 32366 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - NYLHA: October 7, 1997; 32365 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - NYLHA: Annual Meeting, 1997; 32364 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Presidential Pardon: Stanley Feingold and Joe Galu, 1993; 32363 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - PSC/CUNY Savings Account, 1992; 32362 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence: Press, Dan, 1991; 32361 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - ADA National Convention, 1999; 32360 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - ADA Convention: Bosnia Resolution, 1993; 32359 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - ADA: Schumer Meeting Names and Addresses, 1997; 32358 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - DC 37 Interview, 1999; 32357 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - ADA Long island Exec. Comm.: Voting Inequalities, 1997; 32356 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - VanHees, Mindy, 1999; 32355 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - lowey, Nita, 1999; 32354 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Letter Re: Exec Comm. Action on Kosovo, 1999; 32353 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - ADA Long Island: Resolution on Kosovo, 1999; 32352 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - ADA Paid-up Members: 1st Quarter, 1999; 32351 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - ADA Nominations Comm., 1999; 32350 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - ADA Long Island Exec. Comm.: February, 1998; 32349 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - ADA Long Island Exec. Comm.: October, 1998; 32348 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - ADA National, 1998-1999; 32347 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - ADA long Island, 1998; 32346 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - ADA Long Island Elections, 1998; 32345 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Elder Hostel: Honduras, Guatemala, Belize, 2000; 32344 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Iraq-U.S., 1991; 32343 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Peace in Stages: Israel, 1990; 32342 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Israel: Contemporary Developments, 1980s; 32341 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1987-1989; 32340 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Fitness Club: Great Neck, Undated; 32339 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1990-1992; 32338 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - ADA Long Island, 1989; 32337 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ADA Long Island Meetings, 1987-1988; 32336 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Socialist International Meetings, 1990; 32335 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth Review Incident, 1990; 32334 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Jewish Comm. (LI): Bd. of Governors, 1985-1988; 32333 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - AJC (LI): Gary Sazer, 1988-1989; 32332 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dike, Rad, Undated; 32331 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, 1988; 32330 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Adelman, Nora, 1990; 32329 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - FDR-Humphrey Dinner, 1990; 32328 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Humphrey-FDR Dinner, 1991; 32327 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - International Resolutions, 1990; 32326 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - ADA Long Island Leaflet, 1990; 32325 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ADA Long Island: Congressman, 1990; 32324 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - ADA NYS Lobbying Day: Albany, Undated; 32323 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ADA National Office Directives, 1989-1990; 32322 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bonds: Tripp and Co., 1991; 32321 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: January-April, 1995; 32320 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Forward (Jewish), 1988; 32319 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous, 1990s; 32318 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Government Activism, 1987; 32317 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Bush Admin.: Kamber Group and Civil Rights, 1989; 32316 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Selby, Stella, Undated; 32315 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - TIAA, 1994; 32314 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - US Army: Medals, 1993-1994; 32313 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gotbaum, Vic, 1997; 32312 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Girard, Harlan (Non-Lethal Weapons), 1996; 32311 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - BB to Vic Gotbaum: International Correspondence, 1979; 32310 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Gotbaum, Betsy, 1979; 32309 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Kramer, Gail, 1996-1997; 32308 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Lefkowitz, Hugh, 1994; 32307 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Levine, Bob (USSR), 1991; 32306 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Levine, Mickey: Memoirs, Undated; 32305 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Levine, Mickey, 1997; 32304 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Levine, Mickey: Memorial, 1997; 32303 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Long island Progressive Coalition: Social Justice Comm., 1998; 32302 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Prescriptions, Undated; 32301 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1993-1994; 32300 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - United Nations: WVF, 1996; 32299 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - WVF, 1997; 32298 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - ADA Long Island, 1999; 32297 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - American Jewish Comm., 1999; 32296 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Bosnia, 1996; 32295 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Epstein, Bill: Luncheon, 1999; 32294 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Netherlands Discount Tickets, Undated; 32293 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Israel, 1998; 32292 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Luba, Sy (a/c), Undated; 32291 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - New Jersey Statute on Gypsies, etc., 1997; 32290 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - NYLHA: January, 1999; 32289 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - North Shore Hospital, 1997; 32288 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - NYLHA: Fall, 1998; 32287 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - NYLHA: Constitution, 1997; 32286 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - NYLHA: Brenda Zwiekel, 1998; 32285 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence: November-February, 1981; 32284 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence; June-October, 1990; 32283 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1973; 32282 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence: March-May, 1992; 32281 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Israel: Speech, 1990; 32280 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Speech: Israel Visit - Hamas Fundamentalists, 1993; 32279 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Speech: Peace Now in Israel, 1993; 32278 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: June-June, 1974-1975; 32277 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Hemg, Sue, 1963-1964; 32276 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hanover, New Hampshire, 1961; 32275 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hanover, New Hampshire, 1958; 32274 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Freidel, Frank, 1950-1953; 32273 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Karmi, Nachman and Sara, 1960s-1970s; 32272 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Israel-Arabs, 1947-1993; 32271 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - University of Utrecht (Papers), 1966-1967; 32270 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1982; 32269 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1960; 32268 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1994; 32267 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1999; 32266 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jan 2000-Feb 2000; 32265 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sepersky, Letter to, 1994; 32264 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1997-May 1997; 32263 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1997-Nov 1997; 32262 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1998-Mar 1998; 32261 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Seperky, Letter to, 1994; 32260 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NYS-ADA Constitution, 1985; 32259 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - ADA Coordinating Council-History, Undated; 32258 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Legislators Addresses, 1987; 32257 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ADA Testimonial Remarks, 1993; 32256 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ADA Westchester, 1987-1991; 32255 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ADA: Albany, 1990-1991; 32254 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1995-Dec 1995; 32253 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NYS-ADA Dispute, 1985; 32252 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jillson, Irene, 1992-1993; 32251 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Berger, Henry: Regulation Letter to, 1994; 32250 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Schneier, Ned: NYS-ADA, 1992-1993; 32249 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rich, Evelyn, 1989-1993; 32248 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1983-Nov 1983; 32247 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Friends), 1958-1959; 32246 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education License to Teach, 1949; 32245 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Housing: Public/American Veterans Comm., 1940s; 32244 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1957; 32243 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1983-May 1984; 32242 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Winnant, John (Europe), 1951-1953; 32241 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - European Trip, Jul 1951; 32240 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.: Dissertation on, 1949-1951; 32239 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Wells, John, 1961; 32238 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wellesley Summer Institution, 1947; 32237 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cooper Union Address, Dec 1961; 32236 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Cooper Union: Course Notes, 1952-1953; 32235 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1968; 32234 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Academic Freedom Comm. (AFC): 50th Anniversary, 1976; 32233 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1961; 32232 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Winant, John, 1961; 32231 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1971; 32230 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969; 32229 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969; 32228 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - College Records, 1941-1950; 32227 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - CUNY Promotion, 1955-1967; 32226 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1992-Dec 1992; 32225 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Winant, 1950-1959; 32224 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1964; 32223 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1962; 32222 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1963; 32221 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1967; 32220 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1965; 32219 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Personal), 1966; 32218 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Stark, Irwin, 1981; 32217 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1979-Dec 1979; 32216 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AFC: American Civil Liberties Union, 1978; 32215 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Stark, Orwin (Dorson, Norman), 1978-1979; 32214 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Menand, Louis, 1980; 32213 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ILGWU, 1949; 32212 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Politics, 1949-1952; 32211 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Saxe, Emmanuel, 1961; 32210 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Teachers College, 1962-1965; 32209 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1969; 32208 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964; 32207 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961; 32206 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Winant Research Project, 1950-1953; 32205 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1959; 32204 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1959; 32203 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1952-1953; 32202 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Annunziata, Frank, 1974-1981; 32201 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Asher, Bob, 1978-1981; 32200 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Blaesser, Willard, 1985; 32199 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Black and Puerto Rican Student Community: CUNY, 1969; 32198 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, 1946-1951; 32197 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gotbaum, Vic, 1978-1985; 32196 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Great Neck Estates: 75th Anniversary, 1986; 32195 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Harrington, Death of, 1989; 32194 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hendel Memorial Convocation, 1984; 32193 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Union Power and New York, Undated; 32192 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Forward: 90th Anniversary, 1987; 32191 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Radicalism, Undated; 32190 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Union Power and NY Contract, 1984; 32189 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Union Power and NY Reviews, 1984-1985; 32188 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1999-Mar 1999; 32187 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1998-Sep 1998; 32186 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1998-Dec 1998; 32185 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1977-1985; 32184 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1992-Sep 1992; 32183 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1997-Dec 1997; 32182 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1997-Aug 1997; 32181 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - ADA: 50th Anniversary, 1997; 32180 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - USSR History, 1990; 32179 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1998-May 1998; 32178 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1998- Jan 1999; 32177 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1990s; 32176 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (Israel), Jan 1983-Apr 1983; 32175 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Feingold, Stan, 1992-1993; 32174 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Forward Association, 1999; 32173 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Forward Articles, 1999-2000; 32172 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Forverts (Forward: Jewish and Russian), 1999; 32171 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Freedman, Monroe, 1997; 32170 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Goodrich, Michael, 2001; 32169 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Great Neck Home (Bady, Jerry), 2001; 32168 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Great Neck Senior Center, 1999; 32167 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gubic, Marijan, 1999; 32166 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hill, Felicity, 1999; 32165 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - They Were Not Silent: The Jewish Labor Movement and the Holocaust, 1999; 32164 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hospital Mergers, 1999; 32163 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights, Declaration of, 1998; 32162 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Israel, 2001; 32161 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Israel: Analysis, 1999; 32160 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Israel: Clippings, 1996-1999; 32159 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Israel, Steve/Seltzer, Regina (Democrats for Congress), 2001; 32158 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Israel: General, 2000; 32157 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Israel: General, 1998; 32156 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Israel: Tour, 1999; 32155 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Friedman, Tom, 1986; 32154 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Population Movement (Article), 1991; 32153 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Israel: Soviet Aliyah, 1990; 32152 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - One Year After the Assassination: Where Are We?, 1996; 32151 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Israel: Where is It Heading?, 1996; 32150 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Israel: Civil Rights, 1998; 32149 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Yiftah, Kibbutz, 2000; 32148 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Conference of Non-Governmental Organizations (CONGO): Board Meeting, 2002; 32147 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - ADA, 2001; 32146 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Retirement: Kendal on Hudson, 2002; 32145 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - United Nations, 2001-2002; 32144 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - NGO Fundraising, 1997-2001; 32143 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Lyon's Article (France), 2001; 32142 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Jewish Immigrant Experience, 1994; 32141 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Letter from London, 2001; 32140 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Liberalism is Alive and Well (Article), 1996; 32139 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Long Island Railroad (Cell Phone Usage), 1999; 32138 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - McGure, Ron, 2000; 32137 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - McCarthy, Thaddeus, 2001; 32136 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Dr. McKinley, 1998; 32135 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Menon, Bhaskar, 1999; 32134 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Nathan, Clarence (Hankin), 2000; 32133 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament, 2000; 32132 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - North Shore Glass Co., Undated; 32131 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Nyack Hospital, 1999; 32130 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NYC Walks, 1979-1995; 32129 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Photographs (Lawmakers), Undated; 32128 (Box 13, Folder 47)